wbjnews.com 2011-05-11

# Privacy Statement

Thank you for visiting Waste Business Journal's Web site. WBJ recognizes the public's concern about privacy on the Internet and the Web. This privacy statement describes how information will be gathered about you from your visit to our site and how it will be used by the WBJ's Web site operators.

Waste Business Journal will make every effort to protect personal or business information you choose to provide on our Web site in the same way it protects personal and business information provided through other methods.

This privacy statement is provided for informational purposes only. It is not meant to be a contract of any type. Waste Business Journal may change its privacy statement at any time, without prior notice.

Information Collection on this Web Site

If you read or download information:

If you only browse through the Web site, read pages, or download information, the WBJ Web site computer will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. (This is a routine function of Web site computers.) This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

The Internet domain and IP address for the computer you use when visiting our Web site (for example, "yourcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domain);  
The type of Web browser (e.g. Internet Explorer, Netscape) and computer operating system (e.g. Windows, Mac) used to access our site;  
The date and time you visit the site;  
The pages you visit; and  
If you linked to the WBJ Web site from another site, the address of that site.  
We use this information to help us make our site more useful to visitors, to fix problems, and to learn about the number of visitors to our site and the types of technology visitors use. We do not track or record information about individuals, except as described below.

If you send email to a Waste Business Journal email address:

By sending us an electronic mail message, you may be sending personal information (i.e., your name, address, email address, etc.). We may store your name and address, and may share your email with various staff, to address your problem or concern or to answer your question.

Email is not necessarily secure and can be intercepted. WBJ has arrangements with some third parties for online payments.

Other information may be collected on the WBJ Web site through survey or feedback forms or other means.

Links to Non-WBJ (Third Party) Web Sites

This Web site contains links to information located on sites maintained by public agencies and other private organizations. Once you use a link to another agency, organization or company Web site, WBJ privacy standards no longer apply and you are subject to the privacy policy of that Web site.

Web Site Security

For Web site security purposes and to be sure the WBJ Web site remains available to all users, this site uses software programs to monitor Internet network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. Unauthorized attempts to upload information, change information, or cause damage on this Web site are prohibited and may be prosecuted and punished under current state and federal laws prohibiting activity of that nature.
